import React from "react";
import "./style.css";

let QuestionsArr=[
  {
    question:"Javascript is an _______ language?",
    options:["Object-Oriented","Object-Based","Assembly-language","High-level"],
    Answer:"Object-Based"
  },
  {
    question:"Which one of the following also known as Conditional Expression:",
    options:["Alternative to if-else","Switch statement","If-then-else statement","immediate if"],
    Answer:"immediate if"
  },
  {
    question:'The "function" and " var" are known as:',
    options:["Keywords","Data types","Declaration statements","Prototypes"],
    Answer:"Declaration statements"
  },
  {
    question:"Which of the following variables takes precedence over the others if the names are the same?",
    options:["Global variable","The local element","The two of the above","None of the above"],
    Answer:"The local element"
  },
  {
    question:"Which one of the following is the correct way for calling the JavaScript code?",
    options:["Preprocessor","Triggering Event","RMI","Function/Method"],
    Answer:"Function/Method"
  },


  {
    question:"Which of the following type of a variable is volatile?",
    options:["Mutable variable","Dynamic variable","Volatile variable","SouthAfrica"],
    Answer:"Mutable variable"
  },
  {
    question:"In the JavaScript, which one of the following is not considered as an error",
    options:["Syntax error","Missing of semicolons","Division by zero","Missing of Bracket"],
    Answer:"Division by zero"
  },
  {
    question:"Which of the following number object function returns the value of the number?",
    options:["toString()","valueOf()","toLocaleString()","toPrecision()"],
    Answer:"valueOf()"
  },
  {
    question:"In JavaScript the x===y statement implies that:",
    options:["Only Type is Equal","Only Value is Equal","Both Type and Value are Equal","Both are not Same at all"],
    Answer:"Both Type and Value are Equal"
  },
  {
    question:'Choose the correct snippet from the following to check if the variable "a" is not equal the "NULL":',
    options:["if(a!==null)","if (a!)","if(a!null)","if(a!=null)"],
    Answer:"if(a!==null)"
  },
  {
    question:"Which one of the following is an ternary operator:",
    options:["?",":","-","+"],
    Answer:"?"
  },
  {
    question:"Which one of the following operator returns false if both values are equal?",
    options:["!","!==","!=","All of the above"],
    Answer:"!="
  },
  {
    question:"Which one of the following is not a keyword:",
    options:["if","with","debugger","use strict"],
    Answer:"use strict"
  },
  {
    question:"What are the three important manipulations for a loop on a loop variable?",
    options:["Updation, Incrementation, Initialization","Testing, Updation, Testing","Initialization, Testing, Incrementation","Initialization, Testing, Updation"],
    Answer:"Initialization, Testing, Updation"
  },
  {
    question:"A set of unordered properties that, has a name and value is called______",
    options:["String","Array","Serialized Object","Object"],
    Answer:"Object"
  },
  {
    question:"The linkage of a set of prototype objects is known as______",
    options:["prototype stack","prototype","prototype chain","prototype class"],
    Answer:"prototype chain"
  },
  {
    question:"Which one of the following method or operator is used for identification of the array?",
    options:["Typeof","==","===","isarrayType()"],
    Answer:"isarrayType()"
  },
  {
    question:"If a function which does not return a value is known as _____",
    options:["Static function","Procedures","Method","Dynamic function"],
    Answer:"Procedures"
  },
  {
    question:"Which one of the following keywords is used for defining the function in the JavaScript?",
    options:["Void","init","main","function"],
    Answer:"function"
  },
  {
    question:"Which one of the following is not a example of closures?",
    options:["Graphics","Variables","Functions","Objects"],
    Answer:"Graphics"
  },  
]

export default QuestionsArr;